## **Grzegorz Pawlik**

#### Social Media App Developer at ODIGEO

pawlik.gregor@gmail.com

## Summary

I'm a full-stack developer with an emphasis on software development best practices, such as pair programming, test driven development, distributed Git workflows, principles and patterns of OO, MVC and database design. Expertise: - Extensive experience with PHP (Zend, CodeIgniter), MySQL, JavaScript (jQuery, AngularJS), HTML 4/5, CSS 2/3 (LESS, Sass), AJAX, Git, and SVN - Modern web development techniques such as responsive web design, progressive enhancement, and ensuring concise cross-browser compatibility - Exceptional verbal and written communication skills - Design; knowledge of UI design methodologies, significant experience with Photoshop - Working in agile development environments and as part of multidisciplinary teams

## Experience

#### Social Media App Developer at eDreams ODIGEO

May 2012 - Present (3 years)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, WordPress, Drupal, CodeIgniter, Zend, jQuery, AngularJS, XML, JSON, HTML5, CSS3, Sass/Compass, JIRA, Confluence, Git, SVN, Bootstrap, Facebok/Twitter/YouTube API, Jasmine, Documentation, Responsive design - Responsibility for the running and development of all internal social web applications and tools - Development of dynamic web components for the company assets, including twitter-like feeds, widgets and social networking metric systems - Conceptualization, development, and maintainance of a WordPress multi-site system - Creation of a custom CMS for Facebook and micro-site contests - Authored process documentation from end-to-end solutions such as blogs, Facebook contests, and micro-site contests - Coordination across organization for project planning & process review

#### Full-Stack Developer at BlueBirdMedia

July 2011 - May 2012 (11 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, WordPress, Drupal, Joomla, CodeIgniter, Laravel, jQuery, AngularJS, HTML5, CSS3, Sass/Compass, Git, SVN, Bootstrap, Foundation, Facebok API, Responsive design, Adobe Photoshop - Development of websites ranging from small business solutions to community websites receiving +10,000 unique hits a month - Development of Facebook tabs and landing pages

- Management of projects from initial consultation and branding, to website launch and maintenance
- Responsibility for multiple clients and coding projects every day, effective multitasking SEO and Google Analytics analyzing of traffic, bounce rates and conversions MySQL optimization/design for user information, e-mail lists, billing info, addresses, and website performance/statistics

#### Full-Stack Developer at Internet Advantage

January 2011 - August 2011 (8 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, WordPress, Joomla, CodeIgniter, Sitecore, jQuery, XML, JSON, HTML, CSS, Git, SVN, Bootstrap, Foundation, Facebok API - Front end development on multiple CMS platforms (WordPress, Joomla, Sitecore) - Comprehensive website performance and SEO optimizations - Extensive and deep cross browser debugging - Database migrations between several CMS systems - Responding to the clients' issues, offering solutions and ensuring support tickets were being taken care of on schedule

#### Back-End Developer at Web Koncept Studio

September 2008 - November 2009 (1 year 3 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Drupal, Joomla, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Documentation, Adobe Photoshop - Construction, development, coding, debugging, and maintain dynamic websites using PHP - Development of HTML email marketing campaigns - Creating web layouts and banners using Photoshop - Reviewing of code and documentation of proprietary CMS - Reviewing of co-worked code

## Languages

**English** 

**Spanish** 

German

**Polish** 

## Skills & Expertise

**PHP** 

**Web Development** 

**jQuery** 

HTML/XML

Facebook API

**Advanced CSS** 

**JavaScript** 

**MySQL** 

**Twitter API** 

**Zend Framework** 

CodeIgniter

WordPress

**Photoshop** 

HTML

**CMS** 

**CSS** 

### Education

## Wroclaw University of Technology

MSc, Telecommunication Engineering, 2004 - 2010

## Universidad Miguel Hernández de Elche

Informatics and Telecommunications, 2007 - 2009

# **Grzegorz Pawlik**

Social Media App Developer at ODIGEO

pawlik.gregor@gmail.com



Contact Grzegorz on LinkedIn